const questions = [
	{
		id: 21,
		difficulty: 'hard',
		question: 'How many planets did Senator Palpatine represent in the Senate?',
		img: 'mull',
		answer: 'Thirty-six',
		value: 75
	},
	{
		id: 22,
		difficulty: 'hard',
		question:
			"Against whom was Darth Maul's final challenge before becoming a Dark Lord of the Sith?",
		img: 'null',
		answer: 'Darth Sidious',
		value: 75
	},
	{
		id: 23,
		difficulty: 'hard',
		question:
			'Who was the oldest member of the Jedi Council at the time of the battle of Naboo?',
		img: 'null',
		answer: 'Yoda',
		value: 75
	},
	{
		id: 24,
		difficulty: 'hard',
		question: 'What work did Shimi Skywalker do at home to earn extra income?',
		img: 'null',
		answer: 'She cleaned computer memory devices',
		value: 75
	},
	{
		id: 25,
		difficulty: 'hard',
		question: 'How many lightsabers did Anakin use to kill Count Dooku?',
		img: 'null',
		answer: 'Two',
		value: 75
	},
	{
		id: 26,
		difficulty: 'hard',
		question: 'Who was Rogue Seven?',
		img: 'null',
		answer: 'Kasan Moor',
		value: 75
	},
	{
		id: 27,
		difficulty: 'hard',
		question:
			'Which bounty hunter was obsessed with catching and skinning Chewbacca?',
		img: 'null',
		answer: 'Dengar',
		value: 75
	},
	{
		id: 28,
		difficulty: 'hard',
		question: "What was Yoda's species?",
		img: 'null',
		answer: 'Unknown',
		value: 75
	},
	{
		id: 29,
		difficulty: 'hard',
		question:
			'What did Anakin tell Chancellor Palpatine about the Jedi Council?',
		img: 'null',
		answer:
			"That he knew there were things about the force they weren't telling him.",
		value: 75
	},
	{
		id: 30,
		difficulty: 'hard',
		question: "Who was Darth Sidious's apprentice?",
		img: 'null',
		answer: 'Darth Vader',
		value: 75
	}
];

module.exports = questions;